

## BENJAMIN ABITBOL

#### **CONTACT**

055 66 80 262



benjiab@hotmail.com



Netanya, Israel

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Front-End Development
- QA Automation Testing
- **Network Security**
- **Networks & Systems Security**
- Virtualization and Cloud
- **Network Architecture**
- **Digital Marketing**

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML

**CSS** 

JavaScript

React

**Angular** 

**REST** 

**MERN** 

**MEAN** 

Jira

Linux

Windows

Git

Wordpress

#### LANGUAGES SPOKEN

French: Native **English: Fluent** Hebrew: Advanced

#### **EXTRA-ACTIVITIES**

Crypto and Blockchain

 Advisor for Blockchain **Decentralized Projects** 

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-taught Junior Front-End Developer. I have experience developing full-stack applications (MVC architecture, API) following best practices (refactoring, code standards). I have deep foundations in JavaScript.

I am a self-teaching individual at the core, passionate, motivated and dedicated to coding.

Started as a digital marketer (Google adwords & Facebook ads) then worked as a QA in an automation testing team at Checkpoint (System automation testing framework) and took a 3 months' intensive course to study JavaScript and the MEAN/MERN stack to kick-start my new career.

#### EDUCATION

2017 (3months): Intensive Coding Bootcamp – Elevation Academy

2007-2012 : Master Degree with honours - Business School - ISG Paris

2007 : Bachelors of Science - Physics with honours -

College Yabne Paris

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### **Checkpoint, Tel Aviv**

Automation Testing Team | 2017 - 2018

#### Duties and Responsibilities

Performing daily Automation Testing on System (framework based on Java)

Maintain, expand, and improve our automated testing framework Work with Automation team to triage and identify bugs, collaborate with development team to develop comprehensive testing plan Perform product releases

Stay up-to-date with new testing tools and test strategies (Kibana) and improve results

Extensive use of Jira management tool to report and track bugs.

CCSA/CCSE certifications

Extensive use of Linux command line

# **Elevation Academy, Tel Aviv Junior Developer | Coding Bootcamp |**

Apr, 2017 – Jun, 2017

#### Duties and Responsibilities

Led two Hackathons teams building projects using MEAN stack Developed freelance projects: building landing pages from PSD to html/css/javascript (mobile responsive)

Deep Foundations in JavaScript.

### **Digital Marketing Career Digital Marketing Manager at Deloitte, Bill** Tornade and Gigaspaces Technologies | 2014 –2017

#### Duties and Responsibilities

Organization of events on the French Territory Leading Facebook and LinkedIn ads campaigns

**SEO** and **SEM** Optimization

Extensive use of automation tools (Salesforce, Sales Genius, Rainking...)

#### PROJECTS

built using Wordpress

BababoxTV

built using Node, Angularis and MongoDB The Home Cook Hackathon project built using JS/HTML/CSS

My Portfolio